http://www.girlscoutshcc.org/en/our-council/About_GSHCC/privacy-policy.html

MY GS
ABOUT OUR COUNCILAbout GSHCCContact UsCouncil LeadershipFacility RentalsForms and DocumentsGovernanceGirl Scout ShopsAfter-School Partnerships Program Troop Start-Up AssistanceFinancial AssistanceCareersMediaLatest News and UpdatesSTEM Center + MakerSpace VOLUNTEER ACTIVITIES OUTDOOR COOKIES+ DONATE MY GS
Virtual
Contact
Forms & Documents
Español
Shop
About GSHCCContactCouncil LeadershipFacility RentalsForms and DocumentsGovernanceShopAfter-School Partnerships ProgramTroop Start-Up AssistanceFinancial AssistanceCareersMediaLatest News and UpdatesSTEM Center + MakerSpace
Our Council
About GSHCCPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Web site is owned by Girl Scouts Heart of Central California, a
501(c)(3) non-profit organization headquartered Sacramento, CA.  [Our
online properties comprise of, but are not limited to, all pages found
under girlscoutshcc.org.  This privacy policy applies to these sites
and other sites, mobile apps or other online services we operate that
link to this policy (collectively, referred to below as the site).]
Girl Scouts Heart of Central California is committed to respecting
and protecting the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy
discloses how we collect, protect, and use information you provide or
we collect online, as well as how we protect children's privacy. If
our policy practices change in the future, we will let you know by
posting our revised privacy policy on our Web site. By using the pages
on this site or other services covered by the posted Privacy Policy,
you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Personally Identifiable Information. At our site, we do not collect
personally identifiable information from individuals unless they
provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not
require you to register or provide information to us in order to view
our site. Girl Scouts Heart of Central California only gathers
personally identifiable data on our site, such as names, addresses,
Zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted
by a visitor.  Once collected, we may combine this information with
other information collected from external sources.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information.  Girl Scouts Heart of
Central California may automatically collect certain technical
information from your computer such as your Internet service provider,
your Internet Protocol address, your browser type, your operating
system, the pages viewed, the pages viewed immediately before and
after accessing the Web site, and the search terms entered to get to
our site. This information allows us to improve and customize our
services. We and our service providers may collect this information
using “cookies,” which are small text files that many websites save on
your computer, or similar technologies. See the section on “Use of
Cookies and Similar Technology” below for more information.
USE AND SHARING OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
The personally identifiable information you provide is used by Girl
Scouts Heart of Central California and other entities who are involved
in the operation of this site or who provide support for the Girl
Scouts Heart of Central California and Girl Scouts of the USA mission
and programs, for general business purposes and for the purposes for
which you provided the information.  General business purposes
include, for example, Girl Scouts Heart of Central California and Girl
Scouts of the USA membership activities, program participation,
marketing, promotions, and fundraising activities and communications.
The purposes for which you provide information includes our use of
your personally identifiable information to process online
transactions, purchases, and donations, facilitate participation in
Girl Scouts of the USA and Girl Scouts Heart of Central California
programs, promotions and services, or process job applications.  We do
not sell information you provide to us online with third parties.  We
may share personally identifiable information with third parties
including: (i) with other Girl Scout Councils and Girl Scout troops
for administrative purposes relating to a child’s activities with
another Council or their troop; (ii) when the person submitting the
information authorizes us to share it; (iii) when sharing the
information is with a service provider in furtherance of our
operations or the operation of the site, for instance, to process a
purchase or other transaction you make; (iv) to facilitate
participation in Girl Scouts of the USA and Girl Scouts Heart of
Central California programs, promotions, and services, or to engage in
fund raising, marketing communications and promotions; (v) to comply
with legal processes such as a subpoena or court order or to otherwise
protect your or our legal rights; or (vi) for other purposes for which
you provided the information. Girl Scouts Heart of Central California
has no control over or responsibility for the data collection and use
practices of third parties that process online transactions.  For
example, if you make a purchase on our site using a PayPal account or
similar account of a third party payment provider, certain information
is transmitted to the payment provider and is subject to the third
party’s own privacy policy.
Please note that Girl Scouts of the USA provides operational support
for the site and may collect and use personally identifiable
information you provide to the site and other information collected by
the site as described in this policy.  Girl Scouts of the USA will use
any information it collects for the purposes described in this policy
and in a manner consistent with its own privacy policy, which is
available here.  Girl
Scouts Heart of Central California and Girl Scouts of the USA are each
responsible for their own information handling practices.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
Girl Scouts Heart of Central California is committed to providing a
safe, secure, and fun online experience for children who visit our
site. We are dedicated to safeguarding any personally identifiable
information collected online and to helping parents and children have
positive experiences on the Internet.
We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information
from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental
consent. With parental consent, we may collect information from
children under the age of 13 such as: name, address, email address,
account information, and user generated content. This information
allows us to fulfill a requested transaction and facilitate
participation in online programs, keep records, undertake certain
marketing activities, or to otherwise customize or enhance the Web
site experience for children.
Children under the age of 13 may be able to make certain content
such as user generated content visible to others or the public. This
could include, for example, a webpage or parts of webpages operated by
children that have been designed for group or public viewing. However,
absent parental consent, children under 13 would be allowed to display
only limited information such as a first name or unique user name or
other information that does not allow for online contacting by third parties.
Regardless of what information is displayed, parents can revoke
their consent and ask that information about their children be deleted
from the site by contacting our offices by phone at  916.452.9181 or
via email at hello@girlscoutshcc.org.  To do this or to review
personally identifiable information collected from children, we must
verify the identity of the requesting parent. When a parent revokes
consent, we will stop collecting, using, or disclosing information
from that child. To respect the privacy of parents, information
collected and used for the sole purpose of obtaining verifiable
parental consent or providing notice is not maintained in retrievable
form by the site if parental consent is not obtained after a
reasonable time.
Submissions
Girl Scouts Heart of Central California welcomes children to learn
more about our organization and, where appropriate, participate in
polls and surveys, as well as submit comments, artwork, writings, and
other submissions for posting on our Web site. For this reason, Girl
Scouts Heart of Central California follows the guidelines for
interactive electronic media published by the Children's Advertising
Review Unit (CARU) of the Better Business Bureau for pages targeted to
children under 13. However, we encourage this be done only with their
parent's knowledge and supervision. We also encourage children to use
an alias (e.g., "Bookworm", "Skater", etc.), first
name, nickname, initials, or other alternative to full names or screen
names which correspond with an e-mail address for any activities which
will involve public posting.
In keeping with CARU's Principle regarding respecting and fostering
the parents' role in providing guidance for their children, we
encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of e-mail
and other online activities regularly.
USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data may
be automatically collected by the Girl Scouts Heart of Central
California Web site through the use of "cookies" or other
similar technologies such as web beacons. "Cookies" are
small text files a Web site can use to recognize repeat visitors,
facilitate the visitor's ongoing access to and use of the site, and
allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that
will allow content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come
onto a visitor's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by
assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside
the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected
through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most
browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature.
“Web beacons” are a small snippet of code embedded in webpages
typically used to monitor activity on a webpage and transfer or
collect information, such as information about your Internet Protocol
address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located, the
browser type that is accessing the site, and the ID number of cookies
placed on your computer.
Girl Scouts Heart of Central California uses "cookie"
technology only to obtain non-personal information from its online
visitors in order to improve visitors' online experience and
facilitate their visit within our site. Girl Scouts Heart of Central
California may use web beacons to improve website services, conduct
website analytics, first party advertising relating to us and our
sponsors, and to optimize the browsing experience.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit
our Web site. These companies may use non-personally
identifiable information (that is, not including your name, address,
e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and
other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and
services of interest to you on this or other websites. Read more
information about this
practice at http://www.networkadvertising.org
and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES
This site may be linked to other sites and services that are not
maintained by Girl Scouts Heart of Central California. These Web sites
have their own privacy policies, which you should review prior to
visiting them. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites and
provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
OUR SECURITY SAFEGUARD
The safety and security of your online experience is of the utmost
concern to us. We take measures to implement reasonable physical,
electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent
unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the
information we collect online.
Credit Card Safety
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is also
important to us.  For card transactions we process, we use Secure
Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit
card information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is an Internet
encryption technology, and a method of scrambling data as it travels
from your computer to our Web site servers. We also encrypt your
credit card number when we store your order and whenever we transfer
that information to participating merchants.
To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit
sensitive information, check the document for your browser for
indication of an SSL connection (most browsers utilize an unbroken or
closed padlock). Verify that SSL is active before submitting sensitive
information to our server. To double-check, verify that the URL or
Address line of your browser for our site begins with "https."
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to
your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished
using a shared computer.
Children
If you are under 18, you need parent/guardian permission to use a
credit card to make purchases online.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact
us at:
Girl Scouts Heart of Central California 6601 Elvas Avenue,
Sacramento, CA 95819
Phone:  916.452.9181 Monday-Friday, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m. PST
E-mail
You can email us your question at hello@girlscoutshcc.org and we will get back to
you as soon as possible.
Thank you for visiting our site.
This Privacy Policy was last updated in October 2015.
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Jobs
